http://flagstaffslots.com/privacy-policy-2/

PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM  and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes
of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM include FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM. The FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM website is a retail site. By using the FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM website, you
consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM may collect
personally identifiable information, such as your:
– First and Last Name
– Mailing Address
– E-mail Address
– Phone Number
If you purchase FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This
information is used to complete the purchase transaction.
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us.
However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use
certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account
on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c)
signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e)
submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products
and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to,
communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We
also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Use of your Personal Information
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the
services you have requested.
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or
services available from FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM and its affiliates.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or
postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are
prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM , and
they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in
the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply
with legal process served on FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM, or the public.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times
and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM website.
Security of your Personal Information
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM uses the following methods for this purpose:
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is
protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or
alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any
wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect
your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations
inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any
and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be
guaranteed.
Children Under Thirteen
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age
of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for
permission to use this website.
E-mail Communications
From time to time, FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements,
promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication.
Changes to this Statement
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about
significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary
email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by
updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services
– SSL Protocol available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the
modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe
that FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM has not adhered to this Statement, please contact FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM at:
FLAGSTAFFSLOTS.COM
1125 W. Beale St
Kingman, Arizona 86401
Email Address:
fsslots@yahoo.com
Telephone number:
928-753-7753
Effective as of April 3, 2019
SLOT MACHINES FOR SALEAccessories (2)
Arcade Games (1)
Aristocrat Mark6 (3)
Bally Elite V3200 (1)
Bally M9000 (10)
Bally S9000 (7)
Custom Game (1)
IGT Gameking (6)
IGT I-Plus 9 Inch (28)
IGT I-Plus Round Top (28)
IGT S2000 16 Inch (64)
IGT S2000 4 Reel (1)
IGT S2000 5 Reel (18)
IGT S2000 9 Inch (66)
IGT S2000 Barcrest (5)
IGT S2000 Bonus (12)
IGT S2000 Reel Touch (5)
IGT S2000 Round Top (46)
IGT S2000 Vision (10)
Konami Advantage (1)
Konami K2V (16)
Konami Reel (0)
Specials (1)
Uncategorized (37)
Willams Bluebird 1 (35)
Williams Bluebird 2 (9)
